interlude.fm 2018-09-01

# Privacy Policy

Interlude US Inc. (“Interlude” or “we”, “our” or “us”) respect(s) your privacy and we are committed to protect the information that you share with us. We believe that you have a right to know our practices regarding the information we may collect when you visit our website(s) at the address: www.interlude.fm or www.helloeko.com (the “Site”); view and interact with any of the Interactive Videos (as defined below); use our creative studio and related services (“Eko Studio”), including by uploading any video/audio content (e.g.: footage, video clips, graphics, start/end screen images, buttons, designs, etc.) (“Creator Generated Content”), through use of Eko Studio, and through the use of the Interlude Player.

**PLEASE READ CAREFULLY:**

THIS PRIVACY POLICY MAY BE REVISED AND UPDATED FROM TIME TO TIME, WITH OR WITHOUT NOTICE. INTERLUDE SHALL MAKE REASONABLE EFFORTS TO POST A PROMINENT NOTICE IN CASE ANY OF THE TERMS OF THIS POLICY SHALL CHANGE SUBSTANTIALLY. INTERLUDE URGES YOU TO CHECK THE “LAST REVISED” DATE APPEARING AT THE TOP OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY IN ORDER TO BE UPDATED. YOU CAN REVIEW THE MOST CURRENT VERSION AT ANY TIME AT <https://company.helloeko.com/legal/privacy>

BY ENTERING AND/OR USING THE SITE (INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION LINKING TO THE SITE) AND/OR VIEWING OR USING THE INTERACTIVE VIDEOS AND/OR EKO STUDIO AND/OR THE INTERLUDE PLAYER, YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SET FORTH IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY, INCLUDING TO THE COLLECTION AND PROCESSING OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION (AS DEFINED BELOW). IF YOU DISAGREE TO ANY TERM PROVIDED HEREIN, YOU MAY NOT USE THE SITE AND EKO STUDIO, UPLOAD ANY CREATOR GENERATED CONTENT TO EKO STUDIO OR VIEW AND INTERACT WITH ANY INTERACTIVE VIDEO.

1.  **Collection of Information**

Interlude may collect both non-personally identifiable statistical information (“Non-Identifiable Information”) and individually identifiable information (“Personal Information”).

The Non-Identifiable Information may contain, among other things, the Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser language and keyboard language, and surfing patterns. Such Non-Identifiable Information is gathered and recorded while you are using the Site, Eko Studio, or the Player. We may also collect Non-Identifiable Information on the patterns and manner in which end users interactively compose a personalized version (“Unique Video”) of videos based on pre-recorded audio/video segments of such videos (“Interactive Video(s)”). This information may include information on past, present and future patterns of usage of the Interactive Videos and selection of choices in the creation process of the Unique Videos and similar information (collectively “User Interaction Data”).

Personal Information may contain, among other things, your name, email address, age, gender, and other identifiable and/or demographic information provided to Interlude voluntarily when providing us with your contact information and/or opening a Eko Studio Account (as such term are defined under the [Eko Studio Terms of Service](http://company.helloeko.com/about/legal/eko-studio-terms-of-service)) or through the use of the Interlude Player via Interlude’s website, mobile applications or third party websites and applications. Demographic information shall be collected using the Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting Tool. More information can be found here: <https://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/learn/privacy.html>.

2.  **Usage of Information**

The Non-Identifiable Information we collect is used mainly to enhance the user experience on our Site, and in order to improve our services. For example, we are using the Non-Identifiable Information to determine which areas of the Site or which Materials Users like or don’t like based on traffic to those areas on the Site or the Materials. This helps us continue to improve the Site and Materials for you. We may also use the above-described information to tailor our content to suit your needs. In addition, the User Interaction Data may be used for Interlude’s internal research and development, and for marketing purposes, and we reserve the right to receive compensation for providing this information to third parties, including our clients.

The Personal Information is used to personalize the user experience, thus improving and enhancing such user experience. For avoidance of doubt, any Non-identifiable Information connected or linked to any Personal Information shall be deemed Personal Information as long as such connection or linkage exists.

3.  **Sharing the Information with Third Parties**

We will not share Personal Information with any third party. Notwithstanding the aforesaid, we may disclose Personal Information in the following cases: (a) to satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process, subpoena or governmental request; (b) to enforce this Privacy Policy and any of our other terms specified below, including investigation of potential violations of it; (c) to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; (d) to respond to a user’s support requests; (e) to respond to claims that any content violates the rights of third-parties; (f) to respond to claims that contact information (e.g. name, address, etc.) of a third-party has been posted or transmitted without their consent or as a form of harassment; (g) to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Interlude, the Site users, or the general public; (h) when Interlude is undergoing any change in control, including by means of merger, acquisition or purchase of all or substantially all of the assets of Interlude; or (i) when you upload your own Creator Generated Content or create your own Video Project through the use of Eko Studio and the Eko Studio Services. For instructions on how to request a change or a deletion of any Personal Information you have provided to Interlude, please send an email to: support@interlude.fm.

We may share your information with third parties if you submit a Digital Millennium Copyright Act (“DMCA”) Notification (or Counter Notification) as described in our DMCA Policy, or if you are the person responsible for posting the material addressed in the applicable DMCA Notification that is submitted to us.

4.  **Security**

Interlude takes great care in maintaining the security of your information and in preventing unauthorized access to it through the use of appropriate technology and internal procedures. However, Interlude does not guarantee that unauthorized access will never occur.

5.  **Third Party Sites**

While using the Site and/or viewing any of the Interactive Videos you may encounter links to third party sites. Please be advised that the third party sites are independent sites, and Interlude assumes no responsibility or liability whatsoever for them with regard to privacy matters or any other legal matter. Interlude encourages you to carefully read the privacy policies of such third party sites.
